        [CGAA-2541] Any anonymous user (central or licensee): hompage links to "Themes of the Week" page ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2541 ||| Feature: Homepage link to Themes of the Week page ||| Benefit: In order to visit other recently created Theme of the week collections not featured on homepage ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click the title of the currently featured Theme of the week on the homepage or click "More Themes of the Week' ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the "Themes of the Week" at the top<br/>
          Feature: Homepage link to Polls page ||| Benefit: In order to visit other polls not featured on homepage ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click on "more polls" under the homepage poll ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the "Polls" at the top</p>
          Feature: Homepage link to Quizzes page ||| Benefit: In order to view quizzes other than those featured on the homepage ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click "more quizzes" under the featured homepage ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with "Quizzes" at the top<br/>
          Feature: Homepage "read more" link to "All About Alice!" page ||| Benefit: In order to visit one the page of the site with more information about the content creators ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click on "read more" under the heading "All About Alice!" on the homepage
          Feature: Homepage link to All About Alice!
        [CGAA-2536] Any anonymous user (Central or Licensee): homepage social media buttons ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2536 ||| Feature: Homepage links to Alice! social media and sharing ||| Benefit: In order to visit one of the social media accounts for Alice! Health Promotion ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click on a social media button on the homepage
        [CGAA-2535] Any anonymous user (licensee or central site): homepage theme Q&A links ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2535 ||| Feature: Homepage links to individual Q&amp;As featured in theme of the week ||| Benefit: In order to visit one of the five featured theme Q&amp;As on the homepage ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click a linked Q&amp;A title ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the same title at the top<br/>
        [CGAA-2534] Any anonymous user (licensee or central site): recent Q&As ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2534 ||| Feature: Homepage link to recent Q&amp;As ||| Benefit: In order to visit one of the newest and recently updated Q&amp;As on the site ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click on "More Q&amp;As" on the homepage ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the "New Q&amp;As" at the top<br/>
        [CGAA-2533] Any anonymous user (licensee or central site): featured homepage quizzes ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2533 ||| Feature: Homepage links to quizzes ||| Benefit: In order to visit one of the quizzes listed on the homepage ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click a linked quiz title ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the same title at the top<br/>
          Feature: Footer webform links on homepage
        <p>Feature: Homepage Subscribe menu/Get Alice! in Your Box sign up webform ||| Benefit: In order to sign up to receive the weekly GAA! email message ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee user ||| Action: I can click a linked "Get Alice! in Your Box" item
        <p>Feature: Manage users tool ||| Benefit: In order to add/edit/block/delete licensee users ||| Actor: As a logged in central site manager to the licensee site ||| Action: I can click "manage users" on the licensee site ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the same title at the top</p>
        <p>Feature: Link to return to homepage ||| Benefit: In order to return to the GAA! homepage from any other page ||| Actor: As an anonymous user
          Feature: consolidate licensee site question submissions<br/>
          Feature: Delete local resource for licensee site ||| Benefit: In order to remove one of 5 entries for local resources for licensee sites ||| Actor: As an logged in licensee user ||| Action: I can click on "delete this local resource" ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with a question prompt: "Are you sure you want to delete
          Feature: Ability to change user password ||| Benefit: In order to update password after initial log in permissions granted from Columbia ||| Actor: As an logged-in licensee user ||| Action: I can click "edit" under user name ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the form to enter current password, enter/confirm new password, and save</p>
          Feature: Editing local resources ||| Benefit: In order to add information about and display local resources on anonymous view of licensee site ||| Actor: As an logged in licensee user ||| Action: I can click on "edit this information" associated with a given resource type ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the "edit local resource
          Feature: Licensee university-specific GAA! URL ||| Benefit: In order to visit a specific licensee GAA! site ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee site user ||| Action: I can type "goaskalice.<span class="error">&#91;university name&#93;</span>.edu ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the licensee-specific GAA! site for that university</p>
          Feature: Homepage "About Alice!" menu ||| Benefit: In order to visit site pages on the site specific to the history, reader feedback, awards, and creators of the GAA! site ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee user ||| Action: I can click the "About Alice!" menu ||| Outcome: Then I see the drop down menu with "All About Alice!", "Go Ask Alice! History", "Rants &amp; Raves", and "FAQs" options/pages</p>
          Feature: Homepage "Find Help" menu ||| Benefit: In order to visit pages with local emergency and on campus resources ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee site user ||| Action: I can click the "Find Help" menu ||| Outcome: Then I see the drop down menu with "In an emergency" and "On-campus resources" options/pages</p>
          Feature: Homepage Quizzes menu ||| Benefit: In order to visit the quizzes or polls pages ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee site user ||| Action: I can click on the Quizzes menu ||| Outcome: Then I see the drop down menu with the "polls" and "quizzes" listed</p>
          Feature: Homepage Health Answers menu ||| Benefit: In order to visit Q&amp;As organized under the meta categories, themes, and fact sheets ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee user ||| Action: I can click the Health Answers menu ||| Outcome: Then I see the drop down menu with the Q&amp;A meta categories, themes, recent Q&amp;As, and fact sheet</p>
          Feature: homepage logo/link to licensee univ homepage ||| Benefit: In order to visit licensee university homepage from GAA! licensee siteone of the five New Q&amp;As listed on the homepage ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee site user ||| Action: I can click a linked licensee university logo at the top right hand corner of the homepage ||| Outcome: Then I see the page load with the licensee university main homepage</p>
        <p>Feature: Homepage "visit our Emergency page" link to "In an emergency" page ||| Benefit: In order to visit page with emergency resource information ||| Actor: As an anonymous licensee site user ||| Action: I can click a linked "visit our Emergency page" link in the footer of the homepage ||| Outcome: Then I see a page load with the "In an emergency" title at the top</p>
      <link>https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2499 ||| Feature: Homepage poll on Internet Explorer ||| Benefit: Allow users to interact with content in a different way (other than Q&amp;As) ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click on a radio button next to the option I choose and click "vote" at the bottom of the poll to record.
        <p>Feature: Resource links on Licensee site Q&amp;A pages ||| Benefit: In order to find local resources to the licensee location ||| Actor: As an anonymous user on the licensee site ||| Action: I can click a linked local resource ||| Outcome: Then I see the page displaying information added re: selected resource
        <p>Feature: Fact sheets menu on Licensee site ||| Benefit: In order to view one of the fact sheets (either with no local resources, or specific local resources) on the Fact Sheet submenu ||| Actor: As an anonymous user on the Licensee site ||| Action: I can click on the Fact Sheet menu and select one of the fact sheets listed ||| Outcome: Then I view the selected fact sheet (either with no local resources, or specific local resources)
        [CGAA-2504] USER STORY: Viewing local resources on Licensee site ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2504 ||| Feature: "Find Help" menu on Licensee site ||| Benefit: In order to view licensee local resources
        [CGAA-2503] USER STORY: Adding award images on All About Alice! page ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2503 ||| Feature: Add images to stylized basic page ||| Benefit: To successfully post images associated with awards in desired fashion on All About Alice!
        [CGAA-2502] USER STORY: Viewing All About Alice! award images ||| https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2502 ||| Feature: Awards images on All About Alice! page ||| Benefit: In order to view images of awards one of the five New Q&amp;As listed on the homepage<br/>
          Feature: Menu link to top navigation menus on mobile site ||| Benefit: In order to visit any of the top navigation menus (and content listed within) using a mobile version of the site ||| Actor: As an anonymous user ||| Action: I can click on a menu to reveal sub menus ||| Outcome: Then I can navigate through various menus and content on the site</p>
      <link>https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-2500 ||| Feature: Link to create poll ||| Benefit: In order to create weekly poll ||| Actor: As a logged in user with Manager level permissions ||| Action: I can click a linked tool titled "poll" ||| Outcome: I can see the page be redirected to poll creation tool</p>
      <link>https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-218 ||| feature: display timestamp on homepage</p>
        <p>feature: display timestamps on question</p>
        <p>feature: Manager makes change without changing last reviewed on date<br/>
      <link>https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-880 ||| Feature: display of categories to a site visitor</p>
          <b>feature: learn work is ready for my review and have a link to follow</b><br/>
          <b>feature: understand assignment of previous round</b><br/>
          <b>feature: understand what work took place in previous round</b><br/>
          <b>feature: provide feedback on both strengths and needs for improvement</b><br/>
          <b>feature: recommend proceeding to the next task or that the previous assignee do more work</b>
          <b>Feature: reuse content</b><br/>
          <b>Feature: substitute references to local resources on licensee sites</b>
          <b>Feature: structured content</b>
        <p>Feature: Show fields for basic research<br/>
          <b>Feature: New Questions enter workflow</b><br/>
          <b>Feature: Published content needs attention</b><br/>
          <b>Feature: Published content re-enters the editorial workflow</b>
          <b>Feature: Prioritizing submissions</b><br/>
          <b>Feature: manager attention</b>
        <p>Feature: Submitting a question anonymously # Name of the feature<br/>
      <link>https://ownsourcing.atlassian.net/browse/CGAA-598 ||| Feature: consolidated writeups on a health topic</p>
